good morning.
おはようございます
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Oh, wait?
あ、ちょっと?
It looks like you're really nervous.
なんかめちゃくちゃ緊張してるみたいよ
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
perhaps.
たぶん
perhaps?
たぶん?
I don't remember.
覚えてない
Those Hihori were meeting each other for the first time, so their bodies overlapped.
あのヒホリたちは、初対面だから体を重ね合わせたんです
I thought we'd become friends, but
仲良くなったつもりだったんですけど、
It's being reset again.
またリセットされてる
So, did you forget?
じゃあ、忘れちゃったの?
About last time.
前回のこと
So, from the beginning, I was a conductor.
じゃあ、最初から指揮の人で
Thank you very much for your help today.
よろしくお願いしますね、今日は
Do you know what we're doing today?
今日は何するかって知ってます?
yes.
はい
What are you doing?
何するの?
I need to stop checking for a moment.
ちょっと確認を止めないと
What are you doing?
何するんですか?
I filmed myself having sex and posted it for the whole world to see.
エッチするとこ撮って、全世界に公開してありますけど、
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Aikasu is cute.
アイカスかわいいね
Your uncle has gained weight, right?
おじさん太ったでしょ?
I've gained a lot of weight.
めっちゃ太ったんですよ
Do you remember that?
そこ覚えてる?
I took a picture last time, but I forgot what name it was called.
前回撮ったんだけど、どういう名前でやってたか忘れてて
Well then, introduce yourself.
じゃあ、自己紹介
May I ask for your name?
名前お願いしていいですか?
Please stop using formula.
フォーミューはやめてね
What should I call you today?
今日何て呼んだらいい?
Aren't you dating someone who looks like you?
似てる人とかっていないんだっけ?
I feel like we've had that conversation before.
その会話、前もした気がするわ
cute.
かわいい
Reno-chan, it's Reno.
リノちゃん、リノだよね
Lina?
リナ?
Lina-chan.
リナちゃん
Isn't it good?
いいじゃないですか?
Are you in need of money?
お金困ってるの?
Of course.
当然ですよ
Everyone is in need of money.
みんなお金困ってます
The only thing I am good at is buying money.
おじさんお金買うだけが取り柄なんで
Crackle crackle.
パチパチパチパチ
This time, Lina-chan will actually be made to feel good a lot.
今回、リナちゃんは実際いっぱい気持ちよくしてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
yes.
そう
Oh, no?
あ、 ダメ?
I agree.
そうだね
Well, okay.
まあ、いっか
Shall we start?
始めちゃおうかね
Can I wait a moment?
ちょっと待っていい?
Do you do tick talk?
ティックトークとかやるの?
I won't do it.
や らない
Can't dance?
踊れない?
I can't dance.
踊れない
It's okay for such a young girl and an old man to go to this love phone.
こんな若い女の子と、おじさんがこのラブホンに行っちゃっていい
Is that so?
んです かね?
Lina-chan too.
リナちゃんもですね
It's still morning, but I'll check the stream.
まだ朝だけど、 配信をチェックします
hey.
ね
It's really effective.
め っちゃ効いてる
It smells amazing.
すごいいい匂いする
i don't know.
知らない
It's really effective.
めっちゃ効いてるじゃん
I'll stop, then.
やめとくね、じゃあ
Well then, let's get ahead of ourselves.
じゃあもう、上抜いちゃおうか
Yeah.
うん
Oh, can you put it behind the sofa?
あ、それさ、ソファーの後ろに置ける?
Back, back, back.
後ろ後ろ後ろ
You know, it's so far behind.
あのさ、すごい後ろ
Oh yeah, there.
そうそう、そこ
beautiful.
綺麗
It's beautiful, isn't it?
綺麗でしょ
dirty?
汚い?
Well then, it's fine here.
じゃあ、ここでもいいよ
It's worse that way, definitely.
そこのほうがやばいよ、絶対
How many people have sex there?
そこで何人もの人がセックスしてくれよ、
There.
そこ
dirty?
汚い?
Well, just pull it out.
そりゃ抜いちゃって
Please remove Zuba as well.
ズバも抜いちゃってください
I also pulled out Zuba.
ズバも抜いちゃって
It's white.
白いね
I like white underwear.
白い下着好き
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
Please turn around.
後ろを向いてください
後 ろを向いてください
Please turn around.
後ろを向いてください
Well, I want to remove the breasts that are currently wearing the white lotus hat.
じゃあ今、白蓮帽してる おっぱいを 取りたいんで、
Shall I take the pella?
ペラ取っちゃいましょうか
Huh?
あれ?
What were you hiding?
何隠してたの?
There's nothing to hide.
何も隠すものないでしょ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
So much so that it was rejected as a natural monument.
天然記念物に否定したくらいですよ
Aren't you sleepy?
眠くない?
Did you sleep well?
しっかり寝た?
I thought I was so nervous that I couldn't sleep.
緊張して眠れないのかと思ってた
That's not true.
そんなことないね
So, can I lick your breasts?
じゃあおっぱい舐めちゃっていい?
Okay.
いいよ
Shall I just take that?
ちょっとそれ取るかな?
I'll lick it.
舐めるね
Because I want to lose weight and eat rice balls, what is your favorite food?
痩せっておにぎりするから、 好きな食べ物は何ですか?
That's what you said last time.
なんか前回言ってたよね
Is it rice?
お米なんだっけ?
Aren't you saying this to try to get an exchange?
交換を狙おうとして言ってんじゃないの?
It's not expensive things, but things that are similar to other people that are called opponents.
高いものじゃなくて、 諸人的なものを 相手と呼ばれるわけ
that's why.
なので
My first meal.
初 めてのご飯
I like Byakuren's mom.
白蓮のママが好きだね
I don't like it if I call it.
かけたら嫌
I don't like it if I put something on it.
なんかかけたら嫌
Don't need anything extra?
余計なもの要らない?
You don't need it.
要らないよ
Aren't you Japanese?
日本人じゃないですか?
He's Japanese.
日本人だもんね
Because it's the ideal erotic adult.
理想エロ成人だから
thank you.
ありがとう
Is it salty?
しょっぱいの?
I don't know.
わかんない
Why are you there?
なんであそこにいてるの?
But, you have a really warm body.
でもね、すっごい体あったかいよ
Warm.
あったかい
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
My body is tall.
体が高い
Aren't you nervous too?
緊張もしてるんじゃない?
I haven't.
してない
That's about shoulder level.
そ こは肩くらだね
It's so warm.
すっごいあったかい
Because I'm sitting.
座ってるから
Hello.
こんにちは
Chat at once.
一回にチャット
I don't like it.
嫌
I'm sad.
悲しんでる
Wasn't that unpleasant?
嫌なことじゃなかった?
Yeah.
うん
Oisho.
おいしょ
How many cups is this?
これ何カップあんの?
what up?
どうした?
It gets in the way of looking into my eyes.
目を見るの邪魔
Is this enough?
これで十分?
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
No.
ダメだよ
That's enough for today.
今日これ、 もういいよ
It's popping all over the place.
ぴんぴんにポッキしてるよ
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
Can you put your hands behind your head?
頭の後ろに両手持ってきてごらん?
I can see my whole mind.
気が丸見え
Do it once.
一回やりなさい
Do it again.
もう一回やって
behind the head.
頭の後ろ
oh yeah.
そうそう
I don't like it.
嫌
Can you try it again?
もう一回やってごらん?
I don't like it.
嫌
It's absolutely beautiful.
全然綺麗だよ
Show me.
見せなさい
It may be growing.
生 えてるかもしれない
Would you hate it if it grew?
生えてたら嫌なの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
From a man's perspective, it's a reward.
男からしたらご褒美ですよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Is there anyone with armpit fetish?
脇フェチの人っている?
Are you there?
いるの?
Armpit fetish.
脇フェチ
Can you try it again?
もう一回やってごらん?
Because it's not Hermon.
ヘルモンじゃないんだから
What is Hermon?
何がヘルモン?
Something is Hermon.
何かがヘルモン
What is Hermon?
何がヘルモン?
Something is Hermon.
何かがヘルモン
This kind of serum comes out on this sofa.
このソファーでこういう 血清が出るよ
Turn to me and stand on the sofa.
そっち向いて ソファーの上に立って あれね、
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Just like that, push like this.
そのままね、こうやってこう押しとしてね
I'll do that.
そうするね
Her butt is so attractive that she can ride it.
お尻がすごい魅力的に乗れるんです
純白
Then it'll just be normal.
じゃあそのまま普通になんだろうな
Shall we sit down like this?
こうやって 座ってみようか
Stand on that sofa.
そのソファーの上に立ってね
Get on your knees like this.
こう やって膝立ちになって
So, I guess I can handle it.
で、手ついてかな
So, start sticking out your butt.
で、お尻つきだして
Shall I come over here for a little while?
もうちょっとこっち来ようか
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
Butt, C7 pieces.
お尻、C7個
different?
違う?
here?
ここ?
Did you do it like this?
こうやった?
Was it there?
そこだった?
different.
違う
here?
ここ?
The crack, here?
割れ目、ここ?
Yeah.
うん
Is it okay here?
ここ はいいの?
Don't like C7?
C7は嫌なの?
I don't like C7.
C7は嫌
I'll take off your pants.
パンツ脱がせるよ
Leave the sofa untouched.
ソファー、手ついたままにしといて
Keep your butt perky.
お尻をプリッとさせたままね
So, can you get your butt out?
で、お尻つきだせる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Well then, wouldn't it be better to go from here?
ちょっとじゃあ、こっちから行くのもよくね?
I'll cut this too.
こっちも切ります
pants.
パンツ
There's nothing.
なんもないじゃん
Beautiful.
きれいな
I like this private power system.
これ、私力系好きやん
The noodles are ephemeral, aren't they?
麺はかないでしょ
Is that so?
そういうこと?
There's no one with noodles in it, right?
麺入ってるやつないでしょ
Because he's not a grandpa.
おじいちゃんじゃないんだから
Menjushi.
めんじゅうし
Do you hate menju?
めんじゅうし嫌だ?
Why don't you come here?
こっち来れば?
I'm scared.
怖いんだ
prohibit.
禁止
eye.
目
I got angry.
怒られちゃいました
Look here.
こっち見て
Look this way.
こっち向いて
So, are you going to turn sideways?
じゃあ、横向いてくの?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Are you heading this way?
こっち向いてくの?
be careful.
気をつけて
Hands behind.
手は後ろ
Pitch black Kurosukega.
真っ黒くろすけが
Why why?
なんでなんで?
My uncle is still alive.
おじさんも生えてるんだよ
There is one pitch-black Kurosuke.
真っ黒くろすけ1匹いるんだよ
Are you cutting it?
切ってるの?
Yeah, I'm cutting it.
うん、切ってる
I don't do that to Piper.
パイパーにはしないんだ
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
feel ill?
気持ち悪い?
This line is just right.
ちょうどいいね、この線で
It's a good line.
いい線入っちゃう
Please avoid feet.
足、避けてください
There's nothing.
何もないよ
You can just see a normal pussy.
普通におまんこが見えるだけだよ
There are people who like this perspective.
この視点が好きな人がいるんですよ
T
T Yes, T.
T そう、T
Is it T?
T なの?
Please fly away and let me do my best.
飛んでさ、コッパリやらせてください
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Just keep doing it.
ずっとやり続けてごらん
I'm putting it in. I'm putting it in.
入れてる入れてる
fool.
バカ
Can you solve the M character?
M字解決できる?
On the side.
そばの上で
Please spread your legs further.
足もっと広げてください
Please expand further.
も っと 広げてください
picture?
え?
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
Please expand further.
もっと広げてください
My breasts are hidden.
おっぱいが隠れちゃってる
Hands are here.
手はこっち
Let's try harder.
も っと頑張ろう
Spread your left leg wider.
もっと左足広げて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Hey, I took it.
ちょ、取っちゃった
Good luck spreading it out.
広げて頑張って
You're sitting on a nice body.
立派な体に座ったね
Is it your father?
お父さんか
I'm your father.
お父さんです
Spread your pussy.
おまんこ広げてごらん
I don't like it.
嫌
There's nothing.
何もないよ
I don't like it.
嫌
Do you think you should quit?
やめとくと思う?
Do you think you should stop?
や めとくと思う?
Fast forward.
ご早送り
I'll leave it to you for quick delivery.
ご早送りお任せします
What's inside the fast-forwarding?
ご早送り中身は?
I'll expand it later though.
後広げるけどね
Well then, thank you for your continued support today.
じゃあ、今日もよろしくお願いしますね
Yes.
は ーい
If you put that on the camera, it would be really dangerous.
カメラにそれかけたらマジヤバいからね
No, no.
ダメだよ、ダメだよ
No.
ダメだよ
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
ダメダメ
This way
こっち
Facing me.
向 いて
Look over here.
こ っち向いて
Stop the shower.
シャワー止めて
Climb up on the railing.
手すりで上がって
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Turn your body towards me.
体こっち向いて
I can't get rid of my uncle's smell.
おじさんの匂いはなかなか取れないよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It smells like saliva.
唾液臭いよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You're so kind.
優しいね
Let's try it again.
もう一回やってみよう
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I don't know.
知ってない
Shall I have it done for you?
してもらってもらおう?
Mange makes a lot of trouble, right?
まんげで凄い荒らすでしょ?
It's dirty here.
ここで汚れてる
That's right.
だよね
Okay.
オッケー
Well, let's wash it off.
じゃあ、洗い流そうか
It's dirty now.
今は汚れてる
Huh?
えっ?
Water is dripping from my mange.
まんげから下垂れ落ちてるよ、水は
One more time.
もう一回
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Oh, thank you very much.
おー、ありがとうございました
Let's try it again.
もう一回やってみよう
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Don't stop.
や めないでよ
やめないでよ
I should have saved the crap for once.
一回クソを取っておけばよかった
He might be a pervert.
変態かもよ
The one you see on the side of the road.
道端で共にいるやつね
Have you ever done it?
やったことある?
Maybe not.
ないかも
I'd like to try it though.
やってみたいけどね
Please stand up.
ひど立ちしてくれ
Here, here, here.
こっちこっちこっち
Just enough natural light.
自然光が当たるくらいで
Please stand up!
ひ ど立ち立ってくれ
Let me put my hands behind my back.
手は後ろにしてもらおう
Let me put my hands behind my head.
手は頭の後ろにしてもらおう
I like it.
好きだね
There are a lot of people who like it.
結構好きな人多いよ
This pose.
このポーズ
Like that cover.
あのあの表紙みたいな
Oh, I love that cover.
ああ、あの表紙かぞっちゃう
Shall we package it like that?
そんな風なパッケージにしてあげようか
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
Aren't these pants?
これパンツなんじゃない?
pants?
パンツ?
Isn't it hidden?
隠れてるんじゃない?
I can't hide.
隠れないよ
It's pants, right?
パンツでしょ
Can I have it after this?
この後いただいちゃっていいんですか?
Please cherish it.
大切にね
Well then, lie down here.
じゃあさ、ここ寝転がってごらん
Which one?
どっちどっち?
If it were here, here, here.
こっちこっちこっちあったら
superior?
上?
Oh, you mean up?
あ、上ってこと?
Probably even higher.
多分上だって
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That's good, Chan.
いいな、ちゃん
It's going up a lot.
めっちゃ上がってる
I thought I'd do it, so I felt like it.
やると思ったから気も合ったよ
Oh, you did it?
あ、やったの?
I thought you'd do it.
やると思ってたんだろ
It's been found.
見つかされてるじゃん
No pants.
パンツダメだよ
From Koshibayu.
こしばゆから
I'll tell you, it's fine.
言うよ、すっていいんだね
I'll tell you, it's okay.
言うよ、すっていい
I'll say it since it's new.
新たから言うよ
Hahaha.
はっはっは
Something...
なんか...
How can I make you angry?
どう やって 怒らせるの?
You don't have to do that.
やらないでいいよ、そこは
That's stupid.
ア ホだ
アホだね
That's stupid.
Can I look at the box?
お箱なびらめしていい?
Please cherish it.
大切にね
What does it mean to be sloppy?
雑になべるってどういうことだよ
Something...
なんか ...
Strongly...
強く...
Are you kind?
優しいの?
that.
それ
Your face stinks, your face stinks.
顔臭いね、顔臭いね
Are you kind?
優しいの?
Did you want to say it?
言いたかった?
I hate to say it, but it's cold.
言いたくないけど、寒い
cold?
寒い?
cold
寒
stomach.
い
It's cold.
寒 いよ
small.
小さい
It's seasonal.
季節者だよ
Observation turn.
お番子観察ターン
Open...
びらびら...
It's short.
短いね
short?
短い?
I'm diving deep inside.
奥に潜り込んでる
Short short.
短い短い
Are you holding it in your hand?
それを手にかかしているの?
It's Bjorn.
ビヨーンって
Eh, that's gross.
え、キモいじゃん
There are people like butterflies.
蝶々みたいな人いるよ
I don't want it to just fly away.
その まま飛んでいけるの嫌だよ
I don't like that.
嫌よ、そんなの
It seems that there is such a thing.
そういうのもあるらしいね
The light is gone, isn't it?
ライトが取れちゃってるんだよね
I'm breaking it.
壊してる
Are you breaking it?
壊してる?
It's a boat.
かいかいだな
and?
そして?
You have money, right?
お金あるんでしょ?
I'll do that.
そうする
I'll buy it at Daiso.
ダイソーで買うわ
It's sold at Daiso.
ダイソーに売ってるよ
It's short.
短いね
Peeling.
むきむき
It's small.
小さいね
small?
小 さい?
It seems cute.
かわいいらしい
Is there a paddle?
かいとかあるの?
cute.
かわいい
Isn't it cute?
かわいくない?
Kuritori-san, I don't know.
くりとりさんわからないけど
What kind?
どんなの?
Everyone, Kuritori-san is so cute.
みんなくりとりさんかわいいよ
It spins around a lot.
でかくにまわるからね
Spread it out.
広げてよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Yeah.
うん
That's okay.
そのくらいは大丈夫
The bottom of the holding membrane is torn.
所蔵膜は下が破れてるね
Can you see that?
そんなの見えるの?
I can see it.
見える見える
It hurt a lot when you first did it, didn't it?
最初さ、 やったときめっちゃ痛かったでしょ?
I don't know.
わかんない
I think it hurt, but...
痛かったと思うんだけど、 それをね、
The holding membrane looks like a donut,
所蔵膜がね、 ドーナツみたいになってるんだけど、
It was torn.
裂けたのよ
That's why it hurts, but...
そこからね、 だから痛いんだけど、
After that tear, it will remain forever.
その裂けたあとはね、 ずっと残り続けるんだよ
why?
なんで?
Because it won't go away.
消えないから
消 えないから
The traces left by the first people will remain forever.
一番最初の人の残した痕跡が、 ずっと残り続けるんだよ
It's engraved into your body.
体に刻み込まれてる
So, whenever you forget, just remove the mango and you'll know.
だから、 忘れたらいつでも、 マンゴー除けば分かるよ
I wonder how it got torn.
どうやって裂けたんだろうって
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Shall we go together?
一緒に行っていくんでは?
Yeah, I like the style.
そうそう、スタイルいいね
How many kilograms do you weigh?
体重何キロ?
Is Max the heaviest?
マックス一番重いの?
Heaviest.
一番重い
What happened?
どうしちゃったの?
I ate it.
食べちゃった
What did you eat?
何食べたの?
cooked rice.
ご飯
Did you just eat rice?
ご飯だけを食べたの?
I made a pot.
鍋しちゃったな
The pot won't get fat, will it?
鍋太らないでしょ
Isn't the pot fat?
鍋太らないの?
Because it will decrease, right?
だって、減るしそうじゃんね
No, all the faces will be reduced.
うそ、全部の顔が減るよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
That thinking is terrible.
その思考、やばい
This is terrible.
やばいよ
If you eat a lot, the pot will also gain weight.
いっぱい食べちゃうと鍋も太ります
Are you feeling irritated?
なんかイライラしてるの?
Is it stress?
ストレスなの?
Is it a growing period?
成長期なの?
It's the season of appetite.
食欲の期でしょ
Will my boobs get bigger?
おっぱいがもっと大きくなるの?
A year of appetite.
食欲の1年
Appetite formula.
食欲の式
This is terrible.
やばいよ
Should something like this be allowed?
こんなこと許されていいんでしょうか?
No.
ダメです
Wasn't it prohibited by law?
法律で禁止されてなかったりしたっけ?
It's prohibited.
禁止です
Shall I go to jail?
刑務所に行っちゃおうか
please.
どうぞ
Okay.
いいよ
I don't like it.
嫌だろ、俺は
Okay.
いいよ
I don't like it.
嫌よ
Ira-chan asked me to do it.
イラちゃんから俺にお願いしたと
I say "Kya".
キャーって言う
You made the first move, though.
ちゃんとでも最初に動いとったもんね、
Remember that?
思い出しね
I'm getting goosebumps.
鳥肌立ってる
Sister, are you feeling sick?
お姉さん、気持ち悪いの?
It's itchy.
痒いな
itchy?
痒い?
Are you getting closer?
近づいてきた?
But breasts.
おっぱいだけど
Be kind.
優しくね
I also like your boobs.
おっぱいも喜んでるね
I'm not happy.
喜んでないよ
Are you not happy?
喜んでないよ?
Lisa understands.
リサには分かるよ
My breasts are crying.
おっぱい泣いてる
Are you crying?
泣いてるの?
I want to see someone like this who doesn't mind babies.
赤ちゃんにそわれなくてこんな人見たいな
Even though it's just to get distracted by the baby.
赤ちゃんにそわれるためなのに
Did you see that there?
あっ ち見たかな?
fear
怖
stomach.
い
My lower back hurts.
腰 痛いよ
My back hurts.
腰痛い
Back pain?
腰痛い?
It's hairy.
毛張ってる
Why did you cut it?
何で切ったんだっけ?
Cut?
切る?
Don't worry.
そるんじゃな
I'll put it up in one day.
1日で張るよ
Come here.
こっち来てくれ
Are you licking your dick?
チクビ舐めてます?
It's kind of salty though.
なんかしょっぱいんだけど
I lied to you.
嘘で舐めたよ
picture?
え?
I'm licking my dick.
チクビ舐めてます
Take it down.
下ろして
School swimsuit.
スクール水着
Lick it gently.
優しく舐めてね
I'll bite.
噛むね
No, no, no.
ダメダメダメ
It's the type that peels well.
しっかり剥くタイプなんだね
Do you want me to cover it?
被せて欲しいの?
No, that's fine.
いや、それでいい
Just peel a banana and eat it.
ちょっとバナナを剥いて食べるんだよね
Wow, scary, scary, scary.
うわ、怖い怖い怖い
scared.
怖い
It sounded scary.
怖 い 音してたね
Like this
こうやって
Are you the type to be patient and peel properly?
我 慢自由ちゃんと剥くタイプ?
That's not good.
まずいじゃん
Is it bad?
まずいの?
Freedom to be patient.
我慢自由って
Please be patient.
我慢してね
Do you have the freedom to be patient?
我慢自由我慢すんの?
Did you hold back when more and more came out?
どんどん出てきたら我慢した?
Hmm.
うーん
Will you understand when you are free to endure?
我慢自由出てきたら分かるの?
It's salty and bitter.
しょっぱ苦いよ
It tastes kind of unpleasant.
なんか嫌な味する
Please be kind.
優しくしてね
It's not here.
ここないね
Isn't it here?
ここないね?
It's not here.
ここないね
Did you have the freedom to endure it?
我慢自由出た?
Now that it's really out.
めっちゃ出た今
Did it come out?
出 た?
What happens when you feel better?
気持ちよくなったらどうなってきたからね
It's no good because it feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよくなったからダメ
No?
ダメ?
Yeah.
うん
Down down down.
下下下
She'll sing soon.
早く歌ってくれちゃう
I don't like it.
嫌よ
I can't sing.
歌えないよ
What's your favorite song?
好きな歌何?
So it's the national anthem after all.
じゃあやっぱ国歌でしょ
Will you sing the national anthem?
国歌歌ってくれない?
I don't like it.
嫌よ
Please, you don't want to sing.
どうか歌いたくないでしょ
Bring my club.
マイクラブ持って
Have them break it.
こわえてもらう
Can you eat wood?
ききを食べれる?
Suntama?
すんたま?
Tamage.
たまげ
Tamage?
たまげ?
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
Well then, I'll ask you to hold it one last time.
じゃあ最後もう一回こわえてもらう
Be patient, be patient, be patient.
我慢自由は我慢せ
picture?
え?
Tell me that you feel like you've gained the freedom to be patient.
我慢自由が出てきたなと思ったと教えて
why?
なんで?
If you feel it.
感じたら
With taste.
味で
I try not to understand.
わかんないようにしてる
Well then, shall I say it now?
じゃあもう言いちゃおうか
It's seriously possible to create a successor to Sway Sway.
マジでスウェイスウェイ後代できてるじゃん
Should I take my wallet a little slower?
財布ちょいゆっくりだほうがいいの?
Slowly, slowly.
ゆっくりゆっくり
Can you come here some more?
もうちょいこっち来れる?
The moment you put it in, it's reactionary, so you have to take it properly.
入れる瞬間、 反動的なんでちゃんと取るか
Can I come in?
入れていい?
Yeah, it's coming out.
うん、出るね
Kito entered.
きとうが入った
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Let's go a little deeper, then.
ちょっと奥行くよ、じゃあ
Should I not wake you up yet?
まだ起こさないほうがいい?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
This is me, Boodie.
俺、ブーディーこれだ
It's not that different.
違ってないね
I suddenly thought it was Disrider.
急にディスライダーだと思って
I'm doing a great job.
すっごい仕事してる
What are you doing?
何してる?
I'm looking at the camera.
カメラ見てる
100 men are watching.
100人って男が見てるから
it hurts?
痛い?
I'm holding back on my pussy now.
今、マンコに我慢してる
I gave out a lot, seriously.
いっぱい出しちゃったよ、マジで
You don't like it?
嫌だぞ?
I'm nervous, I'm nervous.
緊張やる、緊張やる
Can you see my face here?
こっちに顔を見るのか
That's nice, this.
それ、いいね、これ
That's crazy.
それ、やば
Invite the spirit.
精神を誘って
I'll take my time after a while.
ちょっと後、じっくりとおらせ
Just like normal, man, let me stretch your knees.
普通にさ、おひとさん、 膝を伸ばしてもらおう
it hurts?
痛い?
My hands tingle.
手がチクチクする
Are your hands tingling?
手 がチクチクする?
Let me put my feet up, feet.
足立ててもらおう、足
Put your feet up, put your feet up.
足を立てる、足を立てる
Stand your feet up.
足を立てる
oh yeah.
そうそう
I have no muscles.
筋肉がない
Impossible.
無理
Impossible?
無理?
I can't.
できない
できないよ
Are you eating rice?
ご飯食べてる?
Put your hands on your back?
手に、後ろに手をつける?
The one who lived this far.
ここまで生きてたやつ
It's a little harsh though.
ちょっときついけど
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
You can put your hand on my back leg or something.
あと足とかに手置いていいよ
Okay, quite a bit.
いいよ、だいぶ
Smooth, smooth, smooth
さらさらさらさらさらさらさらさ
and others.
ら
Let's have some food here.
こ っちに食べてもらおう
Come with both hands.
両手でこっちについて
Have you eaten?
食べてきた?
Things like the amount of salt.
塩加減とか
Okay, this is it.
いいよ、これで
Is this it?
これで?
Yeah.
うん
You can eat it like this, or in any position you like, but
これで食べてもいいし、 好きな姿勢でいいけど、
Move it to your hips.
腰に動かして
A little bit.
ちょいちょいちょい
OKOKOK, pull it out.
OKOKOK、抜いてごらん
You can rest on your elbows.
肘ついていいよ
Look at your hair.
髪伸びてごらん
Can you take your feet out with me?
こっちと足外に出せる?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
painful?
苦しい?
Yeah.
うん
Can you lift your butt with both hands?
両手のお尻ならひよげる?
Butt?
お尻?
Yes, with both hands.
うん、両手で
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's gutsy, it's gutsy.
ガッツリだな、ガッツリ
Good, finally, finally.
いいよいいよいいよ
Do
し ん ど
stomach.
い
It's hard.
し んどい
Do you want me to tell grandpa?
おじいちに言ってほしい?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I'll tell you.
じゃあ言ってあげるね
I'll do a standing frame.
立ち枠やるよ
The one that came here.
ここに来たやつ
None came out.
出たやつない
Has anyone come out?
出たやつない?
Yeah.
うん
The one that came here.
こっち来たやつ
It's like turning your face towards me.
こっちに顔を向ける感じで
Wave your hand.
手を振って
手 を振って
Don't grow your hair long.
髪を伸ばすな
Stretch your legs.
足を伸ばす
Reach out your hand.
手を伸ばす
Pull it out again.
また 抜いて
Stretch out your cute face.
可愛い顔を伸ばす
That's about it.
これくらいだ
You're fine.
元気だよな
amazing.
すごい
Look, look, look.
ほらほらほらほら
Yeah, it seems like that, right?
そうそうみたいでしょ
Please say ao.
あおーってね
Tinker with it and see.
ちくいじってほらほら
Just say please come inside me.
中に出してくださいって言ってほら
I don't like it.
嫌だな
Do you want to be filled inside?
たっぷり中に出されたいの?
Yeah.
うん
Come on, let it inside.
中に出せよほら
Yeah.
うん
Take it inside.
中に出せよ
Aaaaaaaa.
ああああああ
It's coming out, it's coming out.
出ちゃう出ちゃう
Aaaaaaaa.
ああああああ
Can you hold your legs?
足持てる?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
I'll go.
行くよ
I'm pretty close though.
腰のなき気で近いけど
Because my waist is gone.
腰なくなってるから
I'll do it.
やるよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
nice.
いいね
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
see you.
またね
It was put out a little bit inside, so I thought I'd take a look inside.
ちょっと中に出してあったから、 中 見てみようか
Try putting it in.
入れてみてよ
Let's put it out, right?
出そうでしょ
Is it possible?
いけそう?
It's going well.
いけてる
Excuse the camera.
カメラを失礼します
Sperm.
精子が
I don't like it.
嫌だー
I'll change it without any trouble.
あらずに変えるね
I don't like it.
嫌
There you go.
あらうよ
Judging by the contract.
契約で判断する
what?
何?
Hira is amazing.
ひらがすごいよ
You don't have to cut it out, so try pulling it out and putting it in a little bit.
抜き切らなくていいから、 ちょっと抜いたり入れたりしてみよう
mosquito.
か
Let's pull out a little more.
もう ちょっと抜こう
Yes, pull it out.
はい、抜いて
It's so fluttering.
すっごいひらひらだね
The flesh wall is amazingly fluttering.
肉壁がすごいひらひら
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い痛い
picture?
え?
it hurts?
痛 い?
Do you understand?
分かる?
There's a fluttering.
ひらひらがあるんだよ
So I went in and out and in and out.
そこで、入ったり出したり入ったりして
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well, let's take it out.
じゃあ、抜きましょう
Then please go home without any trouble.
じゃあ、あらずに帰ってくれ
I don't like it.
嫌よー
Hey, I've already cum inside you, so let's take a look inside.
ちょっと、中出しちゃったから、 中見てみようか
Try putting it in.
入れてみてよ
why?
なん で?
Is it possible?
いけそう?
Go, go.
いけて、いけて
Now, please excuse the camera.
じゃあ、カメラを失礼します
Look, sperm.
見て、精子が
I don't like it.
嫌だー
I'll go home without a problem.
あらずに帰るんだよ
I don't like it.
嫌
There you go.
あらうよ
Hira is amazing.
ひらがすごいだろ
It's okay if you can't pull it out for a while,
ちょっと、抜ききれなくていいから、
Let's take it out and put it in a little bit.
ちょっと抜いたり入れたりしてみようか
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Let's pull it out a little more.
もうちょっと抜こう
Yes, pull it out.
はい、抜いて
Yes, put it in.
はい、入れて
There's a lot of flutter.
すっごいひらひらがある
The walls are very fluttering.
壁がすごいひらひらがある
I'm going.
いっちゃいちゃう
picture?
え?
Do you understand?
分かる?
There's a fluttering.
ひらひらがあるんだよ
Do you understand?
分かる?
So I went in and out and in and out.
そこで、入ったり出したり入ったりして
Isn't it in?
入 って ない?
入 ってない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well then, let's go to sleep.
じゃあ、寝きましょう
Well then, please go home.
じゃあ、あらずに帰ってね
I don't like it.
嫌よー
Yes.
はーい